world-dating-partners.com 2009-05-27

# Privacy Policy - Partners and Members - Worlddatingpartners.com

This privacy policy outlines our compliance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. For more information on this please follow this link:  
<http://www.opsi.gov.uk/ACTS/acts1998/19980029.htm>

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for the **World Dating Partners** website. We agree to notify you of:

1\. The organization collecting the information

2\. What information this site gathers/tracks about you

3\. What this site does with the information it gathers/collects

4\. With whom the information may be shared 

5\. What choices are available to you regarding deleting and deactivating the information 

6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information 

7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

8\. Changes in our Privacy Policy 

9\. Contacting us

**1\. The organization collecting the information...**

**World Dating Partners** is a program designed to allow hosts to create and link to a customized site for online dating. To accomplish this, our partners enrol, and then create each site they wish to market. None of the information we gather is permitted to be used by the public, other than logos, splash panels, host handles (if provided), and the partner's site name.

**World Dating Partners** Program is a service offered by Datech Limited to webmasters (hosts). It allows webmasters to have a customizable introduction service in association with Datech Limited. The result of this relationship between webmaster and Datech Limited is called the Partner Program. The webmaster is the Partner (host). No information exchanged with the network partner is used outside of the relationship between Datech Limited and the partner, except that exchanged with tax preparers and for tax purposes only. Even though a friendly business relationship exists, Partners may not view private information on users or members of their Partner Site or **World Dating Partners** Network sites. 

**2\. What information this site gathers/tracks about you...**

World Dating Partners Network gathers two types of information: Information users voluntarily submit to us and information indirectly submitted to us by users. Information users voluntarily submit to us:  
There are two types of user-submitted information we collect: Public and Private. We define Public information as partner information that may be displayed on the site, such as your logo, splash panel graphic, and site name, but cannot be used to produce your real or individual identity. Private information is defined as any information that allows others to contact a partner other than through the **World Dating Partners** Program site. 

**Private:**  
This information is gathered from partners. This information includes the partner's full name, address, phone number, tax identification number, password, and more.

To create a Partner Site, the webmaster is asked for certain personal and business information, such as name, address and VAT, Tax ID or Social Security Number. **World Dating Partners** is a vehicle for other relationship-based sites that link to the **World Dating Partners** database. No personal member’s information is exchanged with the Partner, other than that considered public to all members.

**Public:**  
To accomplish fully integrating a partner's site into the **World Dating Partners** Program, we also collect information such as the site name, logo, and splash graphic. This information is displayed to the Public. 

**3\. What this site does with the information it gathers/collects...**

Information partners submit to the **World Dating Partners** : 

**Public:**  
Public information supplied by the partner is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site. This information is used by visitors to help identify the partner site by branding. Public information cannot be used to identify a specific partner by name, address, etc.

**Private:**  
Email addresses, full name, personal and/or company address, phone numbers, tax status and identification, etc., submitted by partners. Private partner information is not provided to members or other partners, unless permitted otherwise.

**World Dating Partners** :  
Information submitted by the Partner is used for establishing and maintaining a business relationship. No personal or business information is shared outside the relationship between **World Dating Partners** and the Partner. Partners may not view or access private information about members of our site or the Partner’s affiliated site. Partners may change their personal or business information within the partners administration area or by contacting us by email at [partners@world-dating-partners.com](mailto:partners@world-dating-partners.com)  
We use your IP address, server, and browser related information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.

**Database ownership**

All data is under the protection of UK law and the Data Protection Act. The database remains the sole property of Datech Limited. Profiles coming from all sites within the Datech Limited Network of Partners belong to Datech Limited. 

**4\. With whom the information may be shared...**

We do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your partner information except to the Inland revenue for tax purposes. It is the partners responsibility to Pay there own tax on any revenue that they earn from Datech Limited

Our site uses temporary cookies to keep Partner session information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your partner account. If you choose to disable the use of cookies in your browser, most areas of the Service will not function properly. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any partner or member! 

**5\. What choices are available to you regarding deleting and deactivating the information...**

**World Dating Partners** gives enrolled Partners the following options for accessing, deleting or deactivating the information stored in **World Dating Partners** database. You may do this at any time from within the this site account by clicking the Delete link in your administration area – or - You can send email to [partners@world-dating-partners.com](mailto:partners@world-dating-partners.com)

**6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect your information...**

**World Dating Partners** takes every precaution to protect your information and has security procedures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of your user data under our control. The personal registration information collected by **World Dating Partners** is stored in secure operating environments with encryption capabilities that are not available to the public. Only authorized employees have access to your personal information, and Datech Limited has strict rules for employees who have access either to the databases that store user information or to the servers that host our services. While **World Dating Partners** cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur, we make every effort to prevent such unfortunate occurrences. 

**7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information...**

**World Dating Partners** gives registered members the following options for accessing, correcting or modifying the information stored in **World Dating Partners** database. You may update this information at any time from within your account or - You can send email to [partners@world-dating-partners.com](mailto:partners@world-dating-partners.com)

**8\. Changes in our Privacy Policy**  
If our privacy policy changes in a way that will materially affect our partners, we will either notify by email or post notice of any changes on the site. 

**9\. Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: 

World Dating Partners Limited (Head Office)  
The Exchange  
Express Park  
Bristol Road  
Somerset  
United Kingdom  
TA7 8LH  
Tel: +44(0)12 7858 8060  
Fax: +44(0)12 7842 8049
